Meyer总统竞选 宾夕法尼亚
这太不可思议了 真的是
This is so amazing. It is.
嗨 你怎么样? 你是健身了么?
Hey, how are you? Do you work out?
- 你说对了 -谢谢 你怎么样?
- You do. - Thank you. How are you?
你俩是要结婚了么?
Are you two going to get married?
- 和谁? - 她我可高攀不起
- Who? - She's way out of my league.
你还真说对了
That's the correct answer.
- 我们爱你 Tom James -谢谢 我也爱你
- We love you, Tom James. - Thank you. Love you, too.
我是说 在显然可以接受范围内的
I mean, within obviously acceptable
适当的那种爱 嘿 很高兴见到你
propriety and so on. Hey, nice to meet you.
总统肯定喜欢这些头条
President's gonna love these headlines.
"梦幻组合"
"Dream Ticket."
"活力二人组"
"Dynamic Duo."
"Tom James 我们有史以来最好的总统"
"Tom James, Best POTUS We Never Had."
好吧 别给她看到这条
Okay, please don't show her that one.
宾夕法尼亚 我真希望我们可以不用走
Pennsylvania, I wish we didn't have to go.
Tom James真是棒 对不对?
And how great is Tom James, right?
我们很快还会见面的
We'll see you guys soon.
如果我再多吃一些油炸蛋糕
If I have any more of those funnel cakes,
我就不能正好地穿过大巴的门了
I won't be able to fit through the bus door.
这是真话 这些油炸蛋糕好极了
It's true. Those funnel cakes are just great.
我们很快还会见面的 谢谢你们
We'll see you guys soon. Thank you.
你们就逃不开我们了
You won't be able to miss us.
这是真话 因为如果... 我们再吃油炸蛋糕 那我们就会变得特别胖
It's true because if... we'll eat them and then we'll get so fat.
特别胖 谢谢
So fat. Thank you.
谢谢 别 别再说了 停
Thank you. No, don't talk anymore. No.
不 我说的是 Amy Brookheimer有点事情 不是有问题
No, what I said was Amy Brookheimer had issues, not problems.
不，她生气了 她不是气得精神失常了
No, she got mad. She's not mentally mad.
多好的群众 对么?
Great crowds, right?
我是说 你真是票房保证啊 我的朋友
I mean, you are box office platinum, my friend.
总统女士 我是来为你服务的
Madam President, I am here to serve.
你是太阳 我是木星的
You are the sun, I the moon.
卫星 甚至不是比较好的那几个
Of Jupiter. Not even one of the good ones.
起来
Get up.
《纽约时报》关于Tom的人物专栏刚刚发布了
"New York Times" Profile on Tom is just out.
挺不错的 应该叫做"纽约Tom报"
It's great. Should be called the "New York Toms."
让我看看
Let me see.
"过去的四年 让James与现实世界紧紧相连
"Four years away has given James a firm grip on the real world.
像一匹孤狼 独行世间
A lone wolf, he gets it done himself
身边没有应声虫和马屁精
without yes-men and flunkies."
你们知道么 狼其实是群居的动物
You know, a wolf is actually a pack animal.
我觉得我更像一只孤独的松鼠
I'm more of a lone squirrel.
你俩都应该为参加 自行车健康项目 而选辆自行车
You both need to choose bicycles for the Bike For Health event.
山地车 公路车 随便什么
Mountain bike, road bike, whatever.
趣味历史... 莱特兄弟
Fun fact... The Wright brothers
用他们的自行车维修店制造了第一架飞机
used their bicycle repair shop to make the first airplane.
我知道
I knew that.
- 是 Liam 谢谢你回电话 - 起来
- Yeah, Liam. Thanks for calling back. - Get up.
有意思的事儿... 我们在参加竞选活动 又不是烤饼义卖
Fun fact... we're running a campaign here, not a bake sale.
的确如此
Exactly right.
嘿，发生什么了?
Hey, what's going on?
这辆车上有异性间的紧张关系
There is sexual tension on this bus.
从?
From?
Tom
Tom.
到?
Towards?
- 我 - 好吧
- Me. - Right.
你知不知道关于那个孤独的松鼠是怎么评论的?
Did you get a load of that lone squirrel comment?
- 噢 我的天 - 你听说了没?
- Oh, my God. - Did you hear that?
- 那就是说? - 就是这样
- And that means? - Exactly.
- 没错 - 你看到我刚坐下来的时候
- Exactly. - And you saw the way he crossed his legs
他双腿紧并朝着我了吧?
towards me as soon as I sat down?
- 真的是 真的是 - 你看到了么? 天啊
- Totally. Totally. - Did you see that? God.
看吧 事情是这样 我从来没有...
See, the thing is, I never...
- 我从来都没有告诉过你这些 但是... - 嗯嗯嗯?
- I never told you this, but... - Yeah, yeah, yeah?
- 我想那大概是12年前 - 啊哈
- I think it was about 12 years ago. - Uh-huh.
- 我们几乎就... - 亲上了?
- We almost... - Kissed?
- 操上了 - 好吧
- Fucked. - Okay.
- 夫人 Ben来电了 - 哦
- Ma'am, Ben's on the phone. - Oh.
我们要遭遇大风暴了 夫人
We got a storm brewing, ma'am.
是以色列还是中国出问题了?
Is it Israel or is it China?
不是 是一场真正的飓风
No, it's an actual hurricane.
而且它会从后方侵袭北卡罗莱纳州
And it's about to take North Carolina from behind.
我猜 我是必须等飓风过去了才能去那儿 对么
I guess I have to get there after the hurricane's passed, right?
夫人 我们可以在这里追踪风暴 我有一个天气应用软件
Ma'am, we can track the storm from here. I have a weather app.
我们有全速运转的国家气象服务系统 Mike
We have the full power of the National Weather Service, Mike.
是 但是这个软件真的很好用
Sure, but this is a really good app.
我们会保持联系
We'll be in touch.
专线别离身
Stay close to the Bat Phone.
Mike 听着
Mike, listen.
我需要你去放话给更多的评论文章
I want you to get more op-ed pieces out there
关于我选择Tom的真实用意
about how my choosing Tom was an act of real vision
和实际的领导关系 可以么?
and real leadership, okay?
我一直在努力做 夫人 但是他们都疯狂迷恋Tom James
I've been pushing, ma'am, but they're gaga over Tom James.
人们喜欢汤姆 但是 我应该获得肯定 因为是我选了他
People love Tom, but I want to get credit for choosing him.
- 是的 夫人 - 头条思维
- Yes, ma'am. - Headline thought.
我想要更多的头条
I want more headlines.
- 是的 夫人 - 好
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes.
- 你想看看这场风暴么? - 不想
- You want to see the storm? - No.
- 嗨 Sue -先生
- Hey, Sue. - Sir.
- 还在忙 - 是的
- Keeping busy? - Yes.
这里好安静啊
So quiet in here.
就像是放满图书管理员尸体的太平间一样
It's like a morgue full of dead librarians.
我恰好喜欢安静 先生
I happen to like the quiet, sir.
当我忙的时候它能让我好好做事情 就像我现在这样
It allows me to get things done when I am busy like I am now.
是哈 我挺想大家的 甚至也想Kent
Yeah, I miss everybody, even Kent.
好了 跟你说话真是费劲
Well, great struggling to talk to you.
哦 老天 这个地方真是死气沉沉
Oh, God, this place has been dead
自从Doyle走人以后
ever since Doyle left the ticket.
Doyle  Amy  Lee  Karen  Dan
Doyle, Amy, Lee, Karen, Dan.
我是说 这个地方走人的速度比一个中国的渡口都快
I mean, this place is leaking bodies faster than a Chinese ferry.
你知道么? 只要当我
You know what? Just as I
有了一定的职权 那么...
was getting some responsibility, right...
- 嘿 Jonah - 嘿
- Hey, Jonah. - Hey.
- Teddy送来问候 - 别想 你特么敢碰我的蛋蛋试试
- Teddy sends a message. - No, don't you dare touch my balls.
一个笑话在人们
A joke's not a joke
都没有笑之前并不是个笑话
unless everyone can laugh at it.
这就是我必须要预见的事儿...
This is what I have to look forward to...
一大群傻逼的弱智小丑就想抓住我的蛋蛋
A bunch of fucking half-wit jokers trying to grab my balls.
- 你好 先生 - Jonah 你的睾丸还好吗?
- Hello, sir. - How are the testies, Jonah?
呃 它们很好 先生 谢谢你
Uh, they're fine, sir. Thank you.
我们有一些关于乳制品关税会议的笔记资料
We have the notes from the dairy tariffs meetings.
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
把它跟那些个文件都一起放在那边吧
Put it in that pile over there with everything else.
我一会儿会一把火烧掉的
I'll set fire to it later.
有一天我遇见一个单身母亲
I met a single mom the other day
同时身兼数职
holding down several jobs at the same time.
国家安全委员会主席
Head of the National Security Council.
国内政策委员会主席
Head of the Domestic Policy Council.
总司令及总统...
Commander-in-Chief and President...
看看这个家伙 他就是一个全新的我
Just look at this guy. He is the new me.
他是超级版的我
He's super me.
你有着充满传奇色彩的一生
You've lived a very interesting life.
你应该写一个回忆录
You should write your memoirs.
我曾是副总统 他们投票给别的候选者
I was veep, they polled other candidates,
扇我这张松垮的老脸
fucked me in my slack old ass.
- 听起来像不像个畅销书? - 我一定会拜读
- Sound like a best seller? - I'd read it.
不过我什么都读 我喜欢阅读
But I'd read anything, though. I love to read.
你知道 就像...
You know, it's...
健康自行车集会 缅因
你已经跟Tom提过那个时候的感觉了吗?
Have you mentioned that moment to Tom yet?
什么? 你是说... 别说了...
What? Are you... stop...
好了 你只需要小骑一圈
Okay, you're just gonna do a short circuit.
- 好 - 懂了? 然后你得挥挥手
- Yes. - Right? And you may wave if you feel
如果你能够掌控好你的那台机器
that you can keep control of the machine here.
机器?你是说自行车?
The machine? You mean the bike?
- 是的 自行车 不好意思 - 那必须的 我可不能摔跤 你知道的
- Right, the bike. Sorry. - Yeah, I can't fall off, you know.
我可不想摔坏我的乳房 它们可不便宜呐
I don't want to break a tit. They weren't cheap.
你好啊
Hi there.
- 一切就绪? - 是的 我准备好了
- You all set? - Yes, I am.
- Tom 你经常骑车吗? - 哦 上帝 不
- Do you bike much, Tom? - Oh, God, no.
- 基本不骑 - 我也是呢
- Hardly at all. - Me neither.
我确实参加了2008年的环意自行车赛
I did do the Tour of Italy 2008,
不过山上骑行那段实在是太尴尬了
but my mountain times were embarrassing.
- 在这儿呢 参议员 - 你们好
- Over here, Senator. - Hey there.
总统夫人 你会说Tom James是一位明星吗?
Madam President, would you say that Tom James is a star?
不 我不会说Tom James是一位明星
No, I would not say Tom James is a star.
我会说他是一位超级巨星
I would say he's a superstar.
而且我做出了明智之选 你是不是也这么认为?
And I made a good pick. Don't you think I did?
- 是的 你选得好 - 很好
- Yes, you did. - Good.
你看怎么样? 我做的很好吧?
What do you think? Did I do a good job?
- 这是不是一个明智之选? - 我...我...
- Is this a good choice that I made? - I... I...
你的车比我的大好多
Your bike is a lot bigger than mine.
我应该像E.T.(美国电影)里一样 坐在自行车前的车筐里
I should be riding in a basket in the front like E.T.
你想骑在我前面吗?
You want to go ahead of me?
不 你随意就好
No, you just do whatever you want.
或许我会跟得上
Maybe I'm gonna come up.
天 这个镜子不起作用啊
God, this mirror doesn't work at all.
我能看见的就只有我的眼球而已
The only thing I can see is my eyeball.
这场景真是美如画呀 充满活力 动感十足
That's a great image. Vital, dynamic.
自我感觉良好 一切都有条不紊
Self-congratulations are in order.
Amy还在生我的气
Amy's still pissed at me.
因为是我把话放出去
It's 'cause I sent that press release out
说她辞职了是因为她精神不稳定
saying she resigned 'cause she's unstable.
她确实精神不稳定
She is unstable.
不过 这么说出来就是你的不对了
It was a big mistake to say it, though.
很好 又一条Amy的仇恨短信
Great. Another hate text from Amy.
"你昨天在电视上看起来满身大汗
"You looked sweaty on TV yesterday.
你能完成这一转变么?"
Are you going through the change?"
我真希望我能明白积怨世仇是怎么回事儿
I wish I understood vendettas.
它们太费时间了
They're so time-consuming.
欢迎来到超级印钞机
Welcome to the money-making machine.
PKM 办公室 华盛顿特区
欢迎来到超级印钞机
Welcome to the money-making machine.
想来看看我们赚钱的车间吗?
Want to see the room where we make all the money?
或者其他也很赚钱的车间
Or all the other rooms where we also make money.
看见Mike隐射我精神不稳定的那条声明没?
See Mike's statement implying that I was unstable?
- 嗯 看见了... - 他们做了煎饼早餐?
- Yeah, look... - They're doing a pancake breakfast?
有没有搞错 是我在一周以前提议的
Hello, I suggested that a week ago
而我却像是一架经过五角大楼被击落的滑翔机
and I was shot down like a hang glider over the Pentagon.
Amy 留在这儿我会给你提供一个非常好的工作机会 好不好?
Amy, I'm offering you an incredible opportunity here, okay?
所以让我们彻底抛弃所有的"让她跟剪刀保持距离"这种事儿好么
So let's cut out the whole "Keep her away from scissors" Thing.
- 好 - 好了? 啊 Sidney Purcell
- Okay. - Yeah? Ah, Sidney Purcell.
我向你愉快地推荐一位女士 Amy Brookheimer
I offer for your delectation one Miss Amy Brookheimer.
呀 看看我
Well, look at me. I have
比白宫的白宫工作人员还多
more White House staff than the White House.
还有一栋更白的建筑
And a whiter building.
好啦 我希望气氛能有所不同
Well, I hope that it's a different vibe
因为我把那些事儿都抛在了身后了
because I am putting all of that stuff behind me.
- 很好 我们需要一些人... - 在我看来
- Great. We need someone... - Selina
Selina Meyer已经是明日黄花
Meyer is yesterday's news as far as I'm concerned.
很好 因为我有一个需要套过来的GMJ大客户
Good, because I have a big GMJ client I need tied up
而我认为你西翼的关系可以把他挖过来
and I think your West Wing access should bring him right in.
是 是 是 我们可以坑骗拴绑过来那些客户 是吧 Ames?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We can trap and truss him, right, Ames?
是呀 如果人们想去那座背后捅刀的精神病院
Yeah, if people want access to that backstabbing madhouse,
我想我们对他而言是得到大客户的唯一选择了
then I think we're the ones to get it for him.
你也许可以称之为白宫
Maybe you can refer to it as the White House
因为我们的一些客户
since some of our clients
实际上仍然喜欢而且尊重那个地方
actually still like and respect that place.
- 好吗? - 好的 没问题
- Okay? - Yeah, all good.
他在说什么? 我说的就是白宫
What's he talking about? I said White House.
我们给你来一杯无咖啡因的咖啡
Let's get you a decaf.
真是荒唐
This is ridiculous.
我的才智在这里都浪费了
My talents are being wasted here.
- 我就像毕加索 却被困于刷栏杆 - 是的
- I'm like Picasso and I'm stuck painting fences. - Yeah.
Wilkie参议员求着见我
Senator Wilkie has been begging to see me.
还有其他很多人也想和我见面
And lots of other people want meetings, too.
Doyle副总统就是个跛脚鸭(也指不中用的人)
VP Doyle's a lame duck.
你知道对等死的动物要怎么做吗?
And you know what you do with lame animals?
- 悉心照顾 - 开枪打死
- You care for them. - You shoot them dead.
哦 是的 我明白了 实际上长久来看实际上更仁慈
Oh, no, yeah, I got you. Kinder in the long run, actually.
Tom 我能问你个问题吗?
Uh, Tom, can I ask you a question?
当然
Sure.
关于过去的一个小小时刻
It's about a little moment in time.
可能得稍微缩小点范围
Might need to narrow that down a little.
我知道
I know.
在华府的时候 你和我
Back in DC, you and me.
我想可能是12年前
I think it was about 12 years ago.
当然 我... 是的
Sure, I... yeah.
我第一任时 我们曾经经常呆在一起
We used to hang out a lot during my first term.
是Sharpley辩论之后的深夜
It was that late night after the Sharpley debate.
哦
Oh.
- 是的 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- 啊 对 没错 - 没错
- Ah. Yeah, right. - Right.
是的 是的 什么..
Yeah. Yeah. What...
- 我们在那辆出租车里 - 我们在一辆出租车里
- We shared that cab. - We shared a cab.
- 没错 - 绿鞋子的那晚
- Right. - The night of the green shoes.
哦 看看你
Oh, look at you,
还记得鞋子
remembering the shoes.
它们把你的脚磨起泡了
They gave you blisters.
还是... 不 是鸡眼
Or was it... No, it was corns.
或者...
Or...
不 不是鸡眼
No, it wasn't corns.
不是鸡... 我没有鸡眼
Not co... I don't get corns.
总之 我们在我家下车
Anyway, we got out of the cab at my house
然后...
and, um...
我们感觉冷 然后你决定...
the cold got to us and then you decided...
你想走回家
you wanted to walk home.
是的 我很喜欢在夜里散步
Yeah, I love to walk at night.
这是唯一可以好好思考的时间
It's the only time I can think straight, you know,
没有电话和屏幕纠缠
without the phones and screens pestering me.
你还好吗 女士? 你的脸有点红
You okay, ma'am? You look a little flushed.
我提到了车里的那个时刻
I mentioned the moment in the car.
- 然后呢? - 他完全不知道我在说什么
- And? - He had no idea what I was talking about.
- 不是吧 开什么玩笑 - 是的
- No, you're kidding me. - Yeah,
我不想讨论这个 好吗?
I don't want to talk about this, okay?
- 太丢脸了 - 好的 我明白 我明白
- I'm so humiliated. - Okay, I understand. I understand.
- 不 你不明白 - 我明白
- No, you don't. - Yes, I do.
不 你不明白 Gary 你是个男人 好吗?
No, you don't, Gary. You're a guy, okay?
你完全不知道我的意思
You can't have any idea what I'm talking about.
是的 我是男人 Tom也是男人
That's right, I am a guy. And Tom's a guy.
你想让我和谈谈吗 男人对男人?
You want me to talk to him like guy on guy?
不要!
No!
你不要一直什么事都为我做 好吗?
You have to stop doing things for me all the time, all right?
对了 这提醒我
Which reminds me, by the way,
明天的煎饼早午餐我要毫不掩饰的本我出场
I'm going commando at tomorrow's pancake brunch.
- 什么? 连内衣也不要? - 什么?
- What? No underwear? - What?
不是 老天爷 对 那肯定能帮我赢得选举
No. Jesus Christ. Yeah, that'll win me the election.
一张我小妹妹的春光照
A nice shot of my beav.
不 我不要提示 好吗?
No, I want no prompting, okay?
我要单干 连你都不带
I'm going solo. No you, even.
没错 Jamie Dan Egan回来了
That's right, Jamie. Dan Egan is back.
就像牛仔裤和麻疹一样(2015年美国多处麻疹爆发)
Like denim and measles.
Lauren 你看起来美极了
And, Lauren, you look beautiful.
你如此热辣 手里的葡萄酒怎么还这么冷?
How do you keep that white wine so cold looking that hot?
嗯...
Uh...
各位
Everybody.
我只想说谢谢大家
So I just wanted to say thank you
欢迎我流放归来
for welcoming me back from exile.
我终于可以正式宣布
I can finally officially say
Dan Egan解禁了
that Dan Egan has the all-clear.
是的
Yeah.
- 玩的开心 好好享受免费的酒 - 耶 免费酒
- Have fun. Enjoy the free bar. - Yay. Free bar.
这是个毫无灵魂的虚荣与野心的狂欢
Well, this is a soulless parade of vanity and ambition.
很棒吧? 汉堡也很好吃
Isn't it great? Sliders are good, too.
- 哦 我没看到 - 哦
- Oh, I didn't see them. - Oh,
听着 我邀请了Nicola Mortlock
so listen, I invited Nicola Mortlock.
- 你不是和她同居过? - 大概一个月
- Didn't you move in with her once? - For like a month.
她不喜欢我的邋遢以及其他女朋友
She didn't like my untidiness or my other girlfriends.
Amy 我还以为你穿着束缚服 对着药物流口水呢
Amy, I thought you might be in a straightjacket drooling on meds.
我猜Mike McLintock说错了
I guess Mike McLintock was wrong.
对 他什么时候说对过？
Yeah, is he ever right?
希望你的小妹妹烂掉
I hope your vagina falls off.
Amy 老天 你他妈怎么回事?
Amy. Jesus, what the fuck?
- 什么? - 好吧 怎么说的婉转一点呢?
- What? - All right, how do I put this sensitively?
- 别他妈的跟个疯子一样 - 对 我在努力
- Stop acting fucking nuts. - Yeah, I'm trying.
好吧 老天 听着
All right, jeez. Look,
对这些人最好的报复就是
the best way to get revenge on these people
利用他们赚他妈的一大笔 好吗?
is to use them to make a shit load of money, all right?
- Mark Twain说的 - 不 我恨华府
- Mark Twain said that. - No, I hate DC
它把你生吞活剥 再把你拉出来
and it chews you up and it shits you out
然后你就一无所有了
and then you are left with nothing
只剩下冷汗和痛苦的回忆
but the night sweats and flashbacks.
得了吧 你爱华府
Oh, come on, you love DC.
找个方式释放一下吧
Find a way to just sort of release it.
我的个老天爷!
Jesus Christ!
Amy 快停下!
Amy, stop it!
-别叫了 -这样感觉真的很好
- Stop screaming. - That feels really good.
我不管
I don't care.
喂
Hey!
-这个男人在骚扰你吗？ -她没事
- This man bothering you? - She's fine.
-我发誓 我... -你闭嘴
- I swear, I... - You need to stop speaking.
-我在问这位小姐 -好的 好的
- I asked the lady. - Yep, yep, yep.
没什么问题 警官
It's all good, Officer.
-那就别那样大叫 -嗯 好的
- Maybe you don't yell out like that. - Mm-hmm. Yes.
-把别人弄得很紧张 -是的 警官
- Makes people nervous. - Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你管这件事 谢谢你管得这么宽
For this and for your broader service.
-我真的感觉好多了 -好了 你得冷静下来
- I really feel better. - All right, you need to calm down.
去做做水疗 练练普拉提
Go to a spa, take a Pilates class.
或去教堂找个人
Go to a fucking church, find someone there
让他给你一点安定 然后吃上四粒
that has some Valium and take four of them.
-你好 -哦 很高兴见到你
- Hello. - Oh, pleased to meet you.
-Ruth Forrester -我也是 Jonah Ryan
- Ruth Forrester. - Pleasure. Jonah Ryan.
这是我的个人助理Richard Splett
This is my personal assistant Richard Splett.
-Splett吗？ -是Splett
- Splett? - Splett.
-嗯 Splett -请坐
- Uh, Splett. - Please have a seat.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
呃 参议员会过来吗？
Uh, will the senator be joining us?
Ryan先生 我们今天请你过来
Mr. Ryan, we asked you here today
是为了Theodore Sykes的事
with regard to a Mr. Theodore Sykes.
呃 你说Teddy吗
Uh, Teddy.
我们决定对他进行集体诉讼
We're bringing a class action against him
我多么希望你能出庭作证
and we'd like you to testify.
我们都曾经是
We've all been the victims
Teddy性骚扰的受害者
of Teddy's inappropriate sexual behavior.
我是唯一的男……
Am I the only man that he...
-目前来说是的 -好吧
- As far as we know. - Okay, all right.
很显然 此事有些误会
Well, obviously there has been some sort of mistake here
因为Teddy和我之间发生的事
because what happened between Teddy and I
显然不是我自愿的
was not consensual, obviously.
他用手握...抓...
There was the ball... The cupping...
或者说是攥...我的蛋蛋
The grabbing or the... The clutching.
在这儿没有什么和羞愧的 Jonah 尽情倾诉吧
There is no shame here, Jonah. Let it out.
确实没必要羞愧
Oh, I understand there's no shame
因为这仅仅是更衣室里无聊的举动而已
because it was locker room tomfoolery and nothing more.
你是说你没有被侵犯吗?
You're saying you weren't assaulted?
先生 你可以不回答这个问题
Sir, you don't have to answer that.
-哦 这个人是你的律师吗? -不是
- Oh, is this man your attorney? - No.
-严格来说不是的 -我们走 现在就走
- Not technically. - Let's go, right now.
Teddy现在无法再伤害你了
Teddy can't hurt you now.
我不是在担心Teddy 我是在担心你们
I'm not worried about Teddy. I'm worried about you.
我的老天爷啊 你们看起来都跟我一样受
Jesus fucking Christ. You all look like me.
这真是个噩梦
This is a nightmare.
真他妈是个噩梦
It's a fucking nightmare.
有件事我想问清楚
And just so we're clear,
这真的不是一次面试吗?
at no point was this a job interview?
-不是 -好吧 好吧 明白了
- No. - Okay. Okay. Clear,
这可是出乎意料啊
Well, that was unexpected.
是啊 我感觉像是又被人侵犯了 只不过这次是被法律侵犯
Yeah, I feel like I got felt up again, but this time by the law.
告诉我要做什么
Just tell me what I'm doing.
你得处理这次情感上的负面影响...
Well, you're dealing with the emotional fallout of...
-我是说今天的日程 Richard -哦 好吧
- Today, Richard. - Oh, yeah.
你在4点30分和Skellern议员有一个会
Well, you have a 4:30 meeting with Congressman Skellern.
好的 是在乔治城吧? 那我们用滴滴打车?
Okay, that's in Georgetown, right? So we should Uber?
哦 对啊 用滴滴 那样最好了 先生
Oh, yeah, no. Uber, that makes the most sense, sir.
Richard 我看起来不像一个中年妇女吧?
Richard, I don't look like a middle-aged woman, do I?
不像 先生
No, sir.
不过 你的那件紫色衬衫确实
Well, you do have that one purple shirt
看着有点像女式的 不过
that looks a bit blousy, but...
-哦 司机Donald三分钟后到达 -很好
- Oh, we got Donald coming in three minutes. - Great.
好的 这个是Hausman议员
Okay, that's Congressman Hausman.
我记住了 下一个是谁?
I've got him. So who's next?
这个是Cheever议员
This is Congressman Cheever.
-还记得他吗？ -记得
- Do you remember anything about him? - Yeah.
他的左耳朵很大
He's got that big left ear
以微弱优势的票数当选
and he has a small majority
而且他还需要基础设施建设的资金?
and he needs funding for infrastructure?
好的 很好 只不过
Okay, really good. It's just
是他的右耳朵超级大
it's his right ear that's freakishly large.
-不 对他来说是右 对我来说是左 -啊 明白
- No, his right, my left. - Aha, got it. Okay.
女士 这是本次薄饼早午餐的布局
Ma'am, this is the pancake brunch setup.
-综合等候区在这 -嗯
- General holding area here. - Yeah.
果汁和咖啡 加热板和煎锅
Juices and coffees. Hot plates and griddles.
一旦煎饼上出现气泡 你就翻面
Okay, the minute you see bubbles, you flip.
不对 出现小孔的时候才翻面
No, you flip when you see holes.
气泡太早了
Bubbles is too soon.
小孔 不是气泡
Holes, not bubbles.
好吧 我是在出现气泡的时候翻面的...
Okay, I flip at bubbles, but...
有趣的是... 那边有三种糖浆
Fun fact... there are three kinds of syrup.
草莓味 枫蜜味 还有乳酪
Boysenberry, maple, and buttermilk.
酪乳不是糖浆
Buttermilk is not a syrup.
女士 这样说好不好?
Okay, ma'am, what if you said this?
-什么? -谁想吃培根馋得嘴疼?
- Yeah? - Who's achin' for some bacon?
不 算了 我不想再准备了 好吗?
No. Okay, I can't prep anymore, all right?
-真的吗? -我可能会吐到Mike身上
- Really? - I might vomit on Mike.
我坐在这大巴上晕车
This bus is giving me motion sickness.
那好 我来给你弄些莨菪碱贴片
Okay, let me get you a scopolamine patch.
有趣的事实.... 莨菪碱第一次被使用是被捷克斯洛伐克
Fun fact... scopolamine was first used as a truth serum
的州警察当作麻醉药
by the Czechoslovakian state police.
这怎么有趣了?
How is that fun?
-Mel? -Tom.
- Mel? - Tom.
你是变瘦了
Did you lose a lot of weight
还是长了15厘米?
or did you get six inches taller?
我觉得你看起来好极了 身高和体重很搭
I think you look great. Great height and weight.
-总统女士 -是我 哦!
- Madam President. - Yes. Oh!
我认识你 没错 我是认识你的
I know you. Yes, I know you, sir.
-额...-Hausman议员
- Um... - Congressman Hausman.
我们之前见过的
And we met before.
不 夫人 我之前从未有此荣幸见过您
No, ma'am, I have never had the honor.
- 好吧 -这是我妻子Beatrice
- Okay. - This is my wife Beatrice.
-你好 很高兴认识你  -你好
- Hello. How good to meet you. - Hello.
-我喜欢你的胸针 -谢谢
- And I love your brooch. - Thank you.
这是蜂蜜(即honeybee)  Beatrice的Bee
It's a honeybee. Bee for Beatrice.
关于蜂蜜的趣实
Fun fact about the honeybee.
你知道一只蜜蜂一生
Do you know how much honey
能生产多少蜂蜜么?
a honeybee produces in its lifetime?
- 不知道 -好吧
- I do not. - Well...
不是惊人的少
it's either surprisingly little
就是惊人的多
or surprisingly a lot.
交谈 点头 这就是传统的交际礼仪
Chatting, nodding. This is classic mingling.
是 但那是葬礼的交际礼仪
Yeah, but it's funeral mingling.
没人会笑
Nobody's laughing.
她不应该讲我教给她的那些笑话
She must not be using all the jokes I gave her.
就这样吗? 躺在这里?
This is it? You just lie here?
是的 放松
Yeah. Unwind.
发呆
Defocus.
我跟你说过我曾经睡过头么?
Did I tell you I slept in?
-哇  -没错
- Wow. - Mm-hmm.
事实上 我起的很早 但接着我就一直呆在床上
Actually, I got up early, but then I just stayed in bed
在手机上看政客们的信息
looking at Politico.
那个站点已经不行了
That site has turned to shit.
但无论如何...
But anyway...
哦 那是Paula Thorpe吗?
Oh, is that Paula Thorpe?
-你拿起你的黄瓜片了? -是的
- Did you lift your cucumber? - Yeah.
-谁是Paula Thorpe ? -Jensen的参谋长
- Who's Paula Thorpe? - The chief of staff for Jensen.
棒极了 你是来这儿放松的
Fascinating. You are here to relax.
请别再谈工作了
Please stop talking about work.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know.
这真是太舒服了
It's so great.
哇 这音乐真恼人
Wow, this music is so irritating.
天哪 只有你会被伽马波和温顺的鲸鱼惹恼
Jesus, only you could be irritated by gamma waves and a whale.
这只是个抠门的 只提供一丢丢荷荷巴油的瑞士安乐死诊所
This is just a Swiss suicide clinic with a hint of jojoba.
Dan 我做了水疗 很管用
Dan, mm-hmm, I did the whole spa thing and it worked.
-我在这儿呆了 差不多... -七分钟
- I have been here, like... - Seven minutes.
七分钟 是的 足够了
Seven minutes. Yeah, it's plenty.
好 那我们就在你办公室见
Okay, so I'm going to see you at the office.
参议员 你可能已经忘了
You won't remember, Senator,
但是你第一次竞选时是我父亲开车送你去的
but my father drove you when you first ran for office.
-你是George Meredith的儿子 ? -是的
- You're George Meredith's boy? - Yeah.
他近来怎样? 还在酿他的啤酒?
How's he doing? Is he still brewing his own beer?
是的 先生 他酿酒的水平和以前一样
Yes, sir. Still doesn't taste any better.
我可以要几份没放牛奶的煎饼么?
Can I get a short stack made without cow's milk?
你没开玩笑吧? 你不想要牛奶还是...?
Are you serious? You don't want milk or...?
不要 摄入牛奶会让我胀气
No, it makes me gassy.
我的肠子可能胀得像手袋那么大 这可不太好
Which, when you have a bag instead of a bowel, is not good.
Bernie  肠胃怎么样 我的朋友?
Bernie. How's the gut, my friend?
还可以忍受 谢谢你还记得
Tolerable. Thanks for remembering.
我专门用豆奶为你准备了些面糊
I made some batter with soy milk just for you.
我来给你做些煎饼
Let me whip you up some pancakes.
哇
Wow.
好啦
There we go.
谁 额... 谁想吃培根馋得嘴疼?
Who's, uh... who's achin' for some bacon?
和Lambert参议员关系很好
Got a very strong relationship with Senator Lambert.
当然 没人想毁掉一段好的关系
Sure, and nobody wants to ruin a good relationship.
确实 Lambert好像认识Roger Furlong
No, and Lambert kind of knows Roger Furlong,
他经常和前副总统Doyle一起参加例会
who takes regular meetings with VP Doyle,
理论上Doyle是能联系到美国总统的
who theoretically has access to POTUS.
-这就是关系链 -看
- That's the chain. - Look,
你想要关系链么? 这就是了 好吧?
you want a chain? Here's the chain, okay?
-我...- 我 美利坚合众国的总统
- Me... - Me, the President of the United States.
美国总统和她团队的
I have the trust of POTUS
所有高级成员都信任我
and all of the senior members of her team.
等下...
Just...
嘿 Amy
Hey, Amy.
是 很高兴接到你电话 对 Sue就是不情愿
Yeah, good to hear from you. Yeah, Sue just won't do.
- Ben Cafferty  -有时我会觉得她已经不在人世
- Ben Cafferty. - Sometimes I think she's actually dead.
你听说了飓风的消息么?
So did you hear about the hurricane?
Ben 不好意思 我好像打错了
Oh, Ben, I'm sorry, I think I dialed by mistake.
嗨?
Hello?
Paul 我们是否能合作?
So, Paul, do we have your business?
对我来说 偷你的电话成本更低一些 不过嘛...
Be a lot cheaper for me to steal your phone, but...
好吧 我们合作吧
yeah, you do.
-棒极了 -完全可以合作
- Excellent. - You do, absolutely.
- 好的 - 欢迎加入
- Okay, good. - Hey, welcome aboard.
- 你不会后悔的 - 非常感谢
- You're not going to regret this. - Thanks so much.
- 好了 - 我很高兴
- All right. - Very excited.
再见
Bye.
哦 伙计 刚刚真是太特么精彩了
Oh, boy, that was fucking amazing.
- 非常感谢- 干的好 Amy
- Thank you very much. - Great work, Amy.
我简直膜拜你
You have my utmost admiration.
-谢谢 -是的 她拿到了你的客户源
- Thank you. - Yeah, she's also got your client list.
-等等 你什么意思? -别担心
- Wait, what do you mean? - Don't worry about it.
不是所有的客户源 就几个而已
She's not taking all your clients, just a couple.
你知道 Fycorps  Killick & Company  Hemmings
You know, Fycorps, Killick & Company, Hemmings.
不 不 不 这是我的三位一体
No, no, no. That's my holy trinity.
这些是我的大亨 没有这些 我只剩下小亨
Those are my biggies. Without those, all I got is my smallies.
哇 战利品 厉害呀
Well, spoils of war, handsome.
你想要高级客户 多向Amy学习学习 或者超越她
You want top clients, be more like Amy. Or better.
你现在是要把我的停车位
You want to go ahead and give her my parking space
我的办公桌给她吗?
and my desk while you're at it?
现在 听着 Dan 我不想如此不讲理
Now, listen, Dan, I don't want to be unreasonable.
Amy 你想要他得停车位和办公桌吗?
Amy, do you want his parking space and desk?
当然要
Yes, please.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
-不 -怎么了?
- No. - What's wrong?
他是煎饼天才
He's this pancake genius
而我却迷失在了一些蜂蜜轶事中
and I got lost in some sort of a bee anecdote.
听我说 你就是碧昂丝
You listen to me. You are Beyoncè.
-他是备胎小野鸡 -夫人
- He is backup bootie. - Ma'am.
-怎么? -是Ben的电话
- Yeah? - It's Ben.
-嘿 发生什么事儿了? -风暴来临了
- Hey, what's going on? - The storm's happening.
夫人 你最好尽快赶回华府 比醉酒超速驾驶要快才行
Ma'am, you've got to get back to DC faster than a speeding drunk.
北卡罗来纳州要从版本图上吹跑了?
Is North Carolina about to be blown off the map?
是的 六小时后可以看见奶牛在天上飞
Yeah, six hours till flying cow time.
这是一个潜在的悲剧 但对你来说是个好机会
This is a potential tragedy that could be great for you.
好的
Okay.
现在的天气啊
And now the weather.
谢谢 我感到非常...
Thank you. I feel very...
好了 我们扔下Tom返回华府 是吧?
Okay, we'll drop Tom back off in DC, right?
就这样 飓风肯定会来袭
This is it. Hurricane's definitely going to hit.
每个人都会从竞选回来
Everyone's gonna be coming back from the campaign
这个地方会再次热闹欢腾起来
and this joint will be jumping again.
你可真是兴奋呐 不是吗 Ben?
You are really excited about that, aren't you, Ben?
那是 必然的嘛 我是说 没有冒犯之意 Sue
Hell, yes. I mean, no offense meant, Sue,
只剩下我和你的时候 我感觉世界里只有我
but when it's just you and me, it's like it's just me.
好吧 看起来情况很糟
Okay, it's looking bad.
不论是国家气象局
Both the National Weather Service
还是我的手机应用都这么说
and my app are saying this.
好 我们去华府 我们等待飓风过后
Right, so we'll go to DC, we'll wait for the storm to pass,
就出发去北卡罗来纳州
and then we'll head to North Carolina.
或者在飓风来袭之前到达那儿
Or go there right now before it hits.
疯了吧你
That's crazy.
只要飓风一过
Soon as the hurricane has passed,
你就正好在当地民众需要你的时刻出现了
you're right there with the people in their hour of need.
他疯了
He's crazy.
-我喜欢这提议 -你呐?
- I love that. - Do you?
这就是你主宰灾难的方式
That's the way you master a disaster.
嘿 夫人 我有些问题
Hey, ma'am, I've got some issues here.
这可是飓风 就像是 夺命风暴
It's a hurricane, and that's, like, killer wind.
好 我们改变航线
Okay, we're turning this plane around,
直接朝北卡罗来纳州进发
we're heading to North Carolina.
我们州若是处于紧急预警状态
A state of emergency in my state
我们会关闭所有航班行程 损失上百万
would shut down travel, cost millions.
能等几个小时吗?
Can we wait a few hours?
抱歉 我们可没有几个小时来等
Well, we don't have a few hours.
那是James参议员吗?
Is that Senator James?
-嗨 -嗨 Cecile
- Hi. - Hi, Cecile.
是他们把视频对比度调到最大了
Either they have the contrast turned up to max
还是说你的气色本来就这么棒
or you are looking fine.
哦
Oh.
-我们要不...? -哦 对 当然
- Should we...? - Oh, yes, of course.
州长 我肯定你能理解
Governor, I'm sure you'll understand,
我们有些关于国家安全的问题
we have some issues of national security
需要讨论一下下
that have to be discussed.
我本来要谈妥了
I have had it
但一看见她那五官分家的脸
with her category five fucking snoot.
我就...她肯定听不见我们说话是吧?
And... she definitely can't hear us?
-听不见 -或许她会读唇语
- No. - Maybe she can lip-read.
好吧 呃...
Okay, um...
我们把椅子转一个角度吧
let's just swivel the chairs.
老天爷噜
Jesus Christ.
-她知道我们听得见不是吗? -我觉得她并不知道
- She know that we can hear that? - My guess would be no.
-我收到Ben的一条短信 -他说什么?
- I got a text from Ben. - What did he say?
-他说什么? -他说他啥都听不见
- What did he say? - He says he can't hear anything.
给他回复
Just text him back.
看见没 如果封锁航班开始实施
See, I think it would be unfair
对于参议员O'Brien和他的竞选伙伴而言
on Senator O'Brien and his running mate
这个肯定是不公平的
if there were a travel lockdown
因为他们会被困在弗罗里达
because they would be stranded in Florida.
他们不像我们一样可以亲赴灾害现场慰问
They would not be able to visit the disaster site like we could.
就让他们随烧烤酱汁而去吧
Just throwing that into the barbecue sauce.
好的
Right.
坏了 这椅子...
It doesn't work. The chair...
州长 我很遗憾告诉您
Governor, it pains me to say this.
我们会在你的机场降落
I think we're gonna have to ground flights
尽管你反对我们这么做
despite your opinion on this matter.
Cecile 如果你能够发出紧急预警的话
Cecile, if a state of emergency were requested,
我想一份来自联邦资金的绵薄之力可以成为你们的甘露
that could be sweetened by a light dusting of federal funds.
好的 我决定发表声明处于紧急预备状态
Okay, I've decided to request a state of emergency.
谢谢你 州长
Thank you, Governor.
咋样啊?
How about that?
-看看呀 放一万个心啊 -看起来奏效了
- Look at that. Put it here. - Seemed to work.
-你知道你是什么吗? -什么?
- You know what you are? - What?
我的明智之选
A great choice that I made.
好吧 让我们去追逐风暴吧 小婊砸
Okay, let's go storm-chasing, you shitkickers.
这不是飓风 那到底特么是什么?
This isn't a hurricane. What the hell is this?
我的应用上说是和风
My app says moderate breeze.
这些树都没有倒下
These trees are still standing.
我不想看到这些屹立不倒的树
I don't want to look at standing trees.
- 我想说 我的风暴去哪儿了? - 它转向去南边了
- I mean, where is my storm? - It veered south.
- 怎么会这样? - 气压原因
- How? - Barometric pressure.
Mike你那个应用怎么搞得?
How about that app of yours, Mike?
你最好把你花在那上面的钱讨回来
You better get your money back on that one.
它其实免费的
It was actually free.
我更新了软件之后它就出现在我的屏幕上了
I updated my software and it just appeared on my screen.
然后我就 "这是个啥" 接着我就用了
And I was like, "What is this thing?" And I just picked it up.
所以这个风暴现在在往哪儿走?
Where's the storm heading now?
- 佛罗里达州 - 佛罗里达州
- Florida. - Florida.
所以O'Brien和Montez
So O'Brien and Montez
会去拍摄风暴照片? 你是这个意思么?
are gonna get the storm photos? Is that what you're saying?
当时我提出的时候这还绝对是个好主意
This was definitely a good idea when I pitched it.
好吧 我延迟了一堆航班
Well, I grounded flights
而且还把政府救助金送去了别的州
and I diverted federal funds to the wrong state.
我怎么不记得你当时提到这个可能性呢 Tom
I don't remember you pitching that as a possibility, Tom.
有时候你需要赌一把运气
Sometimes you have to gamble.
不幸的是 我们的马没有赢
Unfortunately, our horse did not win.
对啊 肯定没赢
No, it certainly didn't.
它跨第一个栏的时候就绊倒了然后被一枪毙了
It fell at the first fence and it got shot.
然后现在一群法国渣渣把它塞进法式长棍了
And now some French fucker's got it in a baguette.
你以后别给我拿竞选
Don't you gamble with this campaign
和我的总统位置赌运气 好吗 Tom?
and this presidency, okay, Tom?
- 我做错的太多 说话太不过脑子了 我道歉 -对 嗯哼
- Too much too soon. I apologize. - Right. Mm-hmm.
- Ryan先生 - 干什么?
- Mr. Ryan. - Yeah?
来自内阁事务的Louise Benjamin到了 想和您见面
Louise Benjamin from Cabinet Affairs is here for your meeting.
啥? 哦对
What? Oh, yeah.
- 对对 对 对 -好的
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Okay.
- 你好 - 嘿 这是个笑话么?
- Hello. - Hi. Is this a joke?
- 什么? - 说实话 你为啥会在这儿啊?
- I'm sorry? - Honestly, why are you here?
我在核对机构的回应...
I'm collating agency responses...
- 你多高? - 什么?
- How tall are you? - What?
抱歉 女士
I am sorry, ma'am.
很多高个子女人都被骚扰了
A number of tall women were molested
然后Ryan先生也是其中之一
and Mr. Ryan was one of them.
好吧 这是一次竞选访问么?
Okay, and this is a campaigning visit?
是的 你在这里的身份是候选人 而不是总统
Yes, you're here as a candidate, not president.
好吧 那这些人在这儿干啥的
Okay, and what do they do here?
浇筑建筑装饰
Embossed and dentil moulding.
- 哦噢 啥? - 我也不知道
- Uh-huh. Huh? - No idea.
女士 我们还组织了一个制蛋工厂(茄子)的访问
Ma'am, we've also set up a tour of an egg plant.
我指包装鸡蛋的一个工厂 不是那个大型的植物
I mean a plant that packs eggs, not the big vegetable.
- 哦 我明白了 - 感谢解释
- Oh, I see. - Thanks for clarifying.
- 不用谢 - 你好
- You're welcome. - Hello.
- 总统夫人 - 是
- Madam President. - Yes.
- 欢迎 - 哦 谢谢你
- Welcome. - Oh, thank you.
我们本来希望带你去看看工厂
We were hoping to give you a tour of the plant,
但是我们工厂在风暴中受到了一些破坏
but we sustained some damage in the storm and it's not safe.
哦! 哦 那么...
Oh! Oh, well...
我们也会想去看看的 Kent 咱们走
we're gonna want to see that, Kent, right away.
抱歉 还有其他什么的 回车里去
Apologies, et cetera. Back in the car.
这是总统访问 不能看起来像竞选
This is presidential. Can't look like campaigning.
Nick
Nick.
没 我正准备躲到车后面去
Nope, I'm gonna be hiding in the back of a car.
我知道 传记都会自成章节
I know. Biography just writes itself.
我们来看看
Let's get a look.
嗯 这个屋顶受到了一些破坏
Well, this roof sustained some damage.
哦 嗯哼
Oh. Uh-huh.
这才不叫破坏
This isn't damage.
- 就是些豆腐渣建筑而已 - 嗯哼
- Just some shitty building. - Mm-hmm.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
O'Brien刚刚从一个房子废墟里拽出一只泰迪熊
O'Brien just pulled a teddy bear out of the ruins of a house.
好 180度大逆转
Okay, complete 180.
这是个竞选访问 把Tom弄过来
This is a campaign visit. Go get Tom now.
- 啊咳! - 你想给我点防晒霜么?
- Ahem! - Want to give me some sunscreen?
- 是啊 - 这外面这么晒
- Yeah. - It's pretty bright out.
外面真是晒
It is so bright out.
- 对吧? - 对 夫人
- Right? - Yes, ma'am.
现在这又是一个竞选访问了
It's a campaign visit again.
嘿 你知道没?
Hey. You see?
总统级别的活动又是另外一回事了
It's a different ball game on a presidential level.
迷人气质也就帮你到这儿了
Charm only gets you so far.
你是对的 夫人 还有很多其他的...
You're right, ma'am. There's a lot more to...
- 我们爱你! Tom! - 因素在里面
- We love you, Tom! - To it than that.
- 嗯哼 你怎么样? - 我很好
- Mm-hmm. How are you? - I'm good.
- 嘿 Tom James - Patrick Murray
- Hey. Tom James. - Patrick Murray.
你在这儿的工作是什么 Patrick?
What do you do here, Patrick?
我基本上是修建房子的边角装饰
I basically cut hard dentil mouldings.
你就是那种我一直想找的人
You're the guy I've been looking for.
我已经在这里工作17年了 夫人
I've worked here 17 years, ma'am.
噢 感谢你
Oh, thank you.
你能在那些硬质木头上雕刻花纹么?
Are you able to emboss harder species of wood?
是的 我们在这里雕刻枫木
Yeah, we emboss hard maple right here.
你能把它合起来么?
Can you combine that?
- 这些雕刻和边角装饰? - 是的 先生 我们可以
- The emboss and the dentil moulding? - Yes, sir, you can.
Sue在么?
Sue around?
呼 谢了
Whew. Thanks.
- 那这是太华丽了 不是么? - 的确
- It's too ornate, right? - Exactly.
你不会想做这玩意的 我知道我不会
You don't want to do it. I know I don't.
嘿 我得打断你了
Hey, I'm gonna have to cut you off.
- 他简直是一个聊天机器 不是吗? - 是的 他的确是
- He's a chatterbox, isn't he? - Yes, he is.
- 来吧 咱们走 - 照顾好自己 Tom James
- Come on, let's go. - Take care. Tom James.
你不用跟他们再打招呼了
You don't have to say hi to them.
我们已经和他们打过招呼了 快走
We've already said hi to these folks. Come on.